I did a video and then when I went to
write the title out I wrote sovereignty
versus social engineering and I was like
nope new video so that is what this
video is the idea of if we're creating a
social media platform Alber creating it
for our own individual selves that there
is a need that's not being met for me
and I need it to be met and looking for
other people who also don't have that
need met and working together to solve
that need or am i trying to socially
engineer the unwashed masses am i trying
to orchestrate the other people aren't
as well informed other people need to
use social media differently or do I
want to use social media differently
because when we can stand in our
sovereignty say what we need out of
social media there is a way to
compromise and create something that's
powerful and meets the vast majority of
about the vast majority of our needs and
the vast majority of people because one
technology can have many benefits and
features and you can turn them on and
off and I can choose to have features
that are sense-making and put them on me
but if I'm trying to socially engineer
the masses I need everyone to use my
tool for sense making or addiction
whatever my thing is I think is wrong
with social media then we're never going
to agree how to how to create that and
therefore we're not gonna have a
threshold of people on it to make it
viable to out-compete gamei in any way
or to have it meet my individual need
that I thought it would meet and it's
definitely not gonna gonna meet
society's needs but if we can stand in
our own individual sovereignty and keep
asking am i trying to engineer other
people am i trying to control other
people or am i trying to solve it for
myself when we can create something
absolutely powerful with and for the
masses and then we get to use it too but
if we need everyone to have the same
tool that we want because we need them
to behave differently we're never gonna
get to that point and so this is what
I'm sitting with sovereignty versus
social engineering and it's a constant
struggle am I trying to control other
people
I know when I'm trying to be controlled
and I do not react well but I trying to
control other people am i trying to make
it so that other people are better
informed are acting different acting
better because all I can truly do is
control myself and together we can
empower ourselves with the tools that we
want and then invite the world if we
have tools for sense-making that we want
to use that are fully transparent and
powerful people enough people will use
them they'll have they'll have a
powerful force in this world so please
like and subscribe and I will see you
next time we are actually doing a
solution raising next Wednesday at 9
a.m. Pacific Standard Time on social
media so tune in for that and if you
want to participate you can email me at
listening inward at gmail.com and I can
send you the link so you can participate
live on camera